Guide to the Computer Services, Academic Computing, User Services records, 1967-1986.
Computer Services, Academic Computing, User Services records,
- John Winters' Files, 1967-1980
  - Manuals, 1968-1977
    - Manuals and Reprints, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Reports and Manuals, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Manuals, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Reprints, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Personal Papers, 1968-1977
    - Affirmative Action Alliance Coordinating Board, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Draft of article (?), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Notes, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Lecture notes, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Lecture notes, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Seminar notes, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Personal, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Computer graphics, story, etc
    - Sue Nadel, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      Miscellaneous OCS and SHARE information
    - Bernie Greenspan, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Student notes
    - Text Collation, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      Notes and reprints
    - Women's Caucus, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Minutes
  - Personnel Files, 1974-1979
    - Dan Boley, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Coordinators, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Coordinators meetings, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Hiring, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Phil Karns, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Doug Neuhauser, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Part time schedules, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Personal, 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Bill Treat, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Steve Worona, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Printouts, 1970-1976
    - TYPIST, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Paper Tape, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
    - Different precisions and modes, 1971 (Box 9)
    - GUESS, 1971 (Box 9)
    - NLLS, 1971 (Box 9)
    - STRUDL, 1971 (Box 9)
    - ALGOL, 1972 (Box 9)
    - ASAP, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Debugging sequence, 1972 (Box 9)
    - PLOT, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Yeats, 1972 (Box 9)
    - CUMC (Medical College), 1977 (Box 9)
    - Notes, comments, complaints (student consultants), 1972-1976 (Box 9)
    - OSIRIS, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Obscure program listings, 1975 (Box 9)
    - FORTRAN (Fred Schneider), 1974 (Box 9)
    - PERT, 1974 (Box 9)
    - SPSS, 1974 (Box 9)
    - FORTRAN H region, 1973 (Box 9)
    - CREATE, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
    - SPIRES, 1979 (Box 9)
    - SPINDEX version GS3005 Special tests and bugs, 1978 (Box 9)
    - SPINDEX version GS3005 System info, 1978 (Box 9)
    - SPINDEX version GS3005 ARP, 1978-1979 (Box 9)